(

poojauidesigner@gmail.com



poojauidesigner.com



Jersey City



I am a UI designer with a background in pastry art, human development, fashion, and interior design. I was born and raised in India and I have always been passionate about design and creativity. I am experienced in communicating with customers and dedicated to understanding what clients want and need. I empathize with clients and take pride in my organizational skills and attention to detail.

EXPERIENCE

UI DESIGNER

Plated Pixiedust- Recipe Developer & Blogger

POOJA JHUNJHUNWALA

2019 to now / Website: www.platedpixiedust.com/ Platforms: @platedpixiedust

- Design website using Squarespace and develop recipes for blog.
- Write and create content- food and lifestyle blog posts, including editing pictures and videos for each recipe
- Share above content on social media platforms such a Instagram, Youtube, Pinterest and TikTok and analyze data pertaining to posts to create content based on engagement.
- Partner with brands by using their products and giving shareable useful feedback to community and create shareable content

Cake by Pooja- Founder and Head Baker

2016 to 2019/ Kolkata, India

Onset Retail store- Intern and Event Managing

November 2011- April 2012/ Kolkata, India

PROJECTS:

- Wagtales- A location based app created using Balsamiq, Sketch and Invision for pet parents to find anything pet related in any area.
- Grocers- An online shopping app designed using Sketch where users can shop their groceries from stores in their area with contact-free delivery.
- Plated Pixiedust- A recipe app created using Sketch, Usability hub and Invision in which users get a step by step recipe and video for each Vegetarian and Vegan recipe.
- Ping- A messaging app mini project created using Sketch and Flinto.
- Remember- A note taking app mini project created using Sketch.
- Poojauidesigner.com Created portfolio website using HTML, CSS and Javascript coding using Atom, Github and hosted on Godaddy.

SKILLS & TOOLS

Sketch Invision Balsamia Flinto Keynote iMovie **User Flows** Competitor Analysis Wire framing Prototyping **Usability Testing** Style Guides & Color schemes Iconography Typography Branding Responsive Design` HTML CSS

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry 2020 - 2021

UI Design Program- An intensive project based course completing many UI/UX projects
Specialization: Front end Development including Javascript, CSS and HTML.

Institute of Culinary Education,NYC 2015-2016

Pastry & Baking Diploma Cake Decoration Diploma

JD Birla Institute, Kolkata 2012-2015

Bsc in Home Science-Human development, Design and Food science

LANGUAGE

English, Hindi, Bengali